(chuckles)
(Leonard:)Oh, hey, Penny, do you want
to go to the airport
(Leonard:)with me later
to pick up my mother?
(Penny:)Sure.
Thanks.
(Penny:)No problem.
Hey, Penny,
(Leonard:)um, since you're already
gonna be at the airport,
(Leonard:)do I need to go?
(Sheldon:)Why don't you want to get
your mother from the airport?
(Leonard:)Well, I can do without
the 40-minute car ride
(Leonard:)where she criticizes
every aspect of my life.
(Sheldon:)She can cover it
in a car ride?
(Sheldon:)I could do 40 minutes
on your posture alone.
(Penny:)You really want me to pick up
(Penny:)your mother all by myself?
(Leonard:)Hmm, I just feel like
(Leonard:)it would be a good chance
for you to bond.
(Penny:)Or a way for you to avoid her?
(Leonard:)I don't know what
he's putting on those cards,
(Leonard:)but you are smarter than ever.
(Penny:)Fine, if you really want me to,
I will pick your mom up.
(Leonard:)Seriously?
(Penny:)Yeah, you know what,
she is my mother-in-law,
(Penny:)and I'd like for us
to have a good relationship.
(Leonard:)That is very mature of you,
(Leonard:)so I'm gonna go ahead
and say, “Suckah.”
(Sheldon:)All right, back to learning.
Okay.
(clears throat)
(Sheldon:)Oh, easy, Bill Nye
the Science Guy.
(Penny:)Or as I know him...
“Creepy old dude
from Dancing with the Stars.”
(Penny:)Ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding!
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪